<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PennyWise</string>
    <string name="_0_0">0.0</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="app_version">Version 1.0.0</string>
    <string name="about_content">PennyWise is a simple and efficient app to manage your personal finances. Track your income and expenses, categorize your transactions, and view detailed statistics to better understand your spending habits.\n\nWith PennyWise, you can:\n• Add and manage income and expenses\n• Categorize transactions\n• View monthly statistics\n• Track your financial progress\n\nDeveloped by Dewmith Mihisara</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">Privacy Policy\n\nLast updated: [Date]\n\nThis Privacy Policy describes how PennyWise collects, uses, and protects your information.\n\nData Collection\n\nPennyWise stores all your financial data locally on your device. We do not collect, transmit, or store your personal information on any external servers.\n\nLocal Storage\n\nAll transaction data, including amounts, categories, dates, and notes, are stored in a local database on your device. This information never leaves your device unless you explicitly choose to share it.\n\nData Security\n\nYour financial data is stored securely on your device using standard Android data storage mechanisms. We recommend that you:\n• Keep your device locked with a secure password or PIN\n• Regularly backup your data\n• Do not share your device with unauthorized users\n\nThird-Party Services\n\nPennyWise does not use any third-party analytics services or advertising networks. We do not share your data with any third parties.\n\nYour Rights\n\nSince all data is stored locally on your device, you have full control over your information. You can:\n• View all stored data within the app\n• Delete transactions at any time\n• Uninstall the app to remove all data\n\nChanges to This Policy\n\nWe may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be reflected in the app.\n\nContact Us\n\nIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us through the app store.\n\nBy using PennyWise, you agree to this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>